Hello everyone!
I'm Hitomi Takamatsu of Equal Love
Moeko Tanizawa of Not equal me
Saya Tanizaki and
Yumi Ozawa of NEAR EQUAL JOY!
Yay!
Yes! That's why
We have come out to Korea!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Yes! So here we are.
As you saw at the end of the last video
Today
Yes!
We're going to have a fashion coordinate showdown.
Here we are at last.
And here we are again, with a bang.
Oh!
There's a line dividing the five teams into two.
The boundary line has been drawn.
Yes, sir.
So...
These two and Nemi here are going to fight it out.
The last video, the last one.
The last game.
We won, and Nemi's team split.
Our team won 400,000 won.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
What? Eh?
Nemi's team.
200,000 won.
That's about 20,000 yen.
Yes, sir.
And there's a theme.
The theme is
This fall's hottest coordinates.
Oh!
Autumnal coordinates
Autumn Codes
I'm going to ask you to wear it.
I've already picked out the team for this one.
Oh, hey.
I was thinking of having you wear it.
I'm thinking of putting together a coordination.
So I'm thinking about that as well.
I see.
Something you wouldn't normally wear?
Yes.
I want to dress her in something she wouldn't normally wear.
You think about it, don't you?
I want to dress her.
I want to dress her up, I want to dress her up
That's right.
I'll try it on, and I'll try it on and I'll try it on.
Yeah.
I want her to look cute.I want to make her look cute.
Yes, ma'am.
Today, I'd like to show you how to dress up.
Yes!
So here we go.
Let's start with the building behind here.
Oh!
Over there!
Wow.
We'll be visiting here first.
Okay.
Well, let's get going.
Let's go.
I'm so happy.
Fast forward.
We're on a bit of a tight budget. That's right.
Sure, just go up. Is it steep?
It's just up here. Wait, look.
Can anyone read? Uniqlo.
Wow, it's true. Uniqlo's kind of a powerhouse, isn't it?
Muji, Daily Casual, Young Street, Young Casual.
Let's go upstairs? Let's go upstairs.
Up there.
Found it.
Young Casual and Young Street.
Oh, it's so cute!
So cute!
The clothes are so cute!
So cute! Cute!
What's one of these like?
Oh, wait.
About 10,000 yen.
We're going with this outfit.
The knit and skirt are over the top.
Oh, no.
Maybe 200,000 won isn't as much as I thought.
Maybe it's difficult.
It's a car zone.
Like this.
It can be like this.
Yes, they can be.
And coats.
We can use four coats, right?
That's right.
And shoes are not included.
They want us to stuff it into the top half.
So cute!
Amazing!
By the way.
How much are these clothes in Korea?
I'm sure.
13,000 yen.
That's nice of us.
Forty thousand.
That's why.
You're lucky it wasn't 200,000.You're lucky it wasn't 200,000.
I'm glad I bought it.
If I'd bought this, I'd have to buy...
One of these.
I'm glad I got it.
I don't even know what a dollar is.
I don't know.
I don't know, I just pick my favorite color or something.
I understand.
But I want you to wear it.
I want you to wear it.
Why?
For Moe.
I'm going to coordinate it with your dolls.
Why not?
I'll dress Saya.
It's so cute!
So cute!
This place is...
We're in a really nice store.
What? This is nice.
They have so many clothes.
It's so cute.
It's like Korean clothes.
I want Saya to wear it.
Today's outfit is very Korean.
So cute!Cute.
Big
sweatshirt
I like brown.
It's nice.
I'll get my own clothes all of a sudden.
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na...
Oh no!
It's red. My hair is red.
It's so cute!
Moe, you're really blue and red!
She's living in penlight colors.
Autumn is brown?
I hate it when you say brown.
Brown!
It's still pretty here.
Like this?
How about this?
What is this?
Are you sure?
By the way, it doesn't taste good?
I didn't write anything about it.
It's not for sale.
I want to win.
If we're going to do this.
I want to win even if I have to spend half the budget.
I want to do my best.
Do you have a bag or something?I don't know if they have bags and stuff.
Certainly.
How much for the bag?
I'm going to pick one that fits the bill.
I'll decide on one and match it with the others.
That's a good idea.
Four hundred and fifty thousand yen.
It's cute.
So cute! It's so cute!
It's not the kind of thing I usually wear.
I'm looking for a mini-length black one.
A leather skirt.
This one!
So cute!
Definitely cute.
Let's go in front of the mirror.
Let's go.
Wait! It's so cute!
This outfit is so cute!
It's rare for Sana to wear this.
I don't think she'll ever wear this.
It's cute.
Really?
It's good.
It's a good idea.
Yeah.
I wonder how much this would cost us in total.
Can I do the math? I'm winning.
Let's do the math.
Thirty-four nine hundred.34900
I'll add... this skirt here...
I'll add...
Oh! I made a mistake!
Tic-toc-toc.
Why do they look so much alike?
Maybe it's Boyo's today.
I got it.
This is probably 45900.
What! Not even close!
You can buy all kinds of accessories with this.
I only spent 12,600.
And maybe another 7400 or so.
Maybe we should go the gray-black route.
Yeah, let's do that.
Okay, well, there's a bunch of stores on this floor.
I'll check out the others.
Let's go with this line.
That's for sure.
Let's look at the others.
Let's look.
It's decided.
Hey!
The gray-black line.
I'll be right back!
Mr. Otsu, I'm going to put on this and use it to get out of the secretary's office.
I'm going to use "I'm going to wear this..." when he comes out of the secretary's office.
Echo aid... it's so cute!
Right: The Kitaike Shinichiroko chain that you don't know aboutRight The Kitaike Shinichiroko Chain that does not know
Karakouaii Scr 900 Makirun
What do you have, everyone? Let's go through and cry
I'm not going to Phys anymore with this person
n RM space, shall we do this?
That's right, that's right, that's wrong
Oh!
Thank you
Thank you very much
Then I was able to complete the setup!
Yay!
Um... Omowaseburi ko...
It's true. It's true.
Oh, it's me.
That's me.
Oh, my God! He's so cool!
He's cute.
This one's cute, too. Cute.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, oh, but maybe a little too much.
A little better price. Better price.
That's ours today.
Might be a little short for us.
Yeah.
What's that first part?
It's a shawl.
I think I might have hit on something.
Hey.
It's going to happen.
What's going on? number of questions
That could be awesome!
Wow!
How was it?
Oh, yes.
Milten.
So cute!
Mucha.
Soya.
Oh!
Like Nyanchu.
We used to do that a lot.
With my friends when I was a kid
That's so cool!
You're good at making money, too.
Nyan chu, nyan chu, nyan chu, nyan chu.
I'm looking at it.
This one's cute, too.
Which one?
Beige-beige.
Suddenly we're talking about something else.
This one's cute, too.
I'm back.We are back!
I'm back.
You might want to decide what you want to knit inside.
Yes, ma'am.
The one below.
The cheap one downstairs.
It's a lightweight knit.
It's nice and light.
I like it in kerottero.
Terrotero is fine.
You're looking for terrotero.
This is good, right?
That's it.
This is it, isn't it?
Hitomi.
This is it.
And for 4,000 yen.
This is it! This is it!
De-da-da-da!
Let's get this one.
Can I buy this?
Let's do this one. Let's do this one.
This is the best one.
Shoes... my own.
Ai, you're wearing the perfect shoes.
Great. Now, Ai...
Now you can step back a bit. Ready?Okay, now, if you'll just step back a little bit.
Look, she's wearing those cute little blue shoes.
Okay, here we go.
You're sure you want to keep these on? Yes, sir.
It's all about the hat. The hat's already gone.
If the hat had gone up in price, we'd be broke.
Are we bankrupt?
We're broke. I'll get it out of you.
The one I just saw...
But it's cute.
Isn't this nice?
But it's cute. It's cute.
I want this one and the bag.
This one's cute. This one's cute, too.
It's so cute! This one's casual.
It's too casual.
You should add a skirt underneath to make it a little sweeter.
There's skirts on the other floors, too.
Let's go look. Let's go look.
Okay, this one's a definite.
Yay. Done.
And accessories and botamus.
And the bill just came to 80,800 won, so...
There's more.
Big stuff.
I cried.
You're so cute.
It's been a while.
I heard it's really bad. I hear it's really bad.
Mine?
What? Is it fixed?
It's looking good.
We've made some progress.
We always do.
Always a step forward.
One step forward.
We've taken a step forward
We've taken one step forward
One step forward
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Let's go buy some caps.
What do you say? If you're the first...
Tense scene.
If the cap costs 10,000 yen...
It's over.
Why are you going to show it?
It's a presentation.
If the cap is 10,000 yen, I'm out.
It's really out.
It can't be more than 7,000 yen.
6,000 yen?
No, this cap isn't 6,000 yen anymore.
Please, please
Please.
6,500 yen.
Is that right? Is that right?
It can't be 4,500 yen.
It can't be 450 yen.
4,500 yen.
Good.
Cute
It's so cute!
How much is it now?
The current price.
362,900 won.
That's about 36,200 won.
So there's only
That's a little over 3,000.
I can use it.
When we go to the accessory store...
Then let's go buy some accessories.
I'll go.
Shall we go downstairs to the cheap place?
Yes, I will.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Get it.
Got it.
We got it.
Okay, let's go.
It's a skirt.
That's a skirt!
Let's go back to this store and seriously look for skirts.
I agree.Yeah.
Hey, hey, hey, wait a minute.
Suddenly...
What's this?
This one's cute, too.
It's cute.
What?
Wait, look.
It's 1,290 yen.
That's still 2,900 yen.
This price comes with this, too.
I'm recommending it today.
I'm sure you'll be able to turn it around.
Certainly.
I'm counting on you.
Please.
Now.
110,700.
117,700 won.
So...
Very much.
Hey.
Wait, I'll go shopping.
I thought...
It's about 80,000 won.
I got it!
Yeah.
You can buy anything you want.Yeah, you can buy anything you want.
I mean, you bought a bag.
I bought a bag and a skirt and a top.
What? Can I buy that?
Yes.
See?
I mean, the base is really Korean.
It's like a Korean accessory.
I can get it for 3,500 yen.
No, but...
The jacket's pretty, but it's cute.
I'll take this one. It's the only one I can think of. It's a little Ivory, you can tell by the white.
But it's the only way to go. Let's do this. Cherish your fate.
I've got about 3,700 yen left. This is 3,500 yen.
It's fate. Let's do this. Cherish your fate.
I wonder... I wonder...
I wonder what it's all about... if we're going out for a day, I'd prefer something a little more autumnal...
It's autumn... it'll be nice if it's autumnal
I think it's the best one near here... and it's more comfortable... because the leather will get nibbled on.
I've got a lot of leather on this one, it'll get nibbled on.
I'll cut this off once and for all.
I wondered how it would turn out, but on the contrary...
I was wondering how it would turn out, but on the contrary, it cost 69,000 won, and it took about 30 minutes.
I'm sure it's great, so I'll just say that it would be great if we could transform ourselves into Saya-chan...
I don't think so, I'll present you Saya-chan, too!
I'm Saya-chan!
So...
I'm so glad I named you!
The time was just in time for me to get there! The time was just right for me.
The time was just in time for me to get together with my friends.
So yes, it's not the same as the first theme.
It's totally different from the first theme of the movie, but it's a very nice alternative to the first one.
Pode a certain something with appenticolors and chi esas nehuey!
Nuh-uh.
tomorrow
Yes, yes, yes, it's important, yes, I choose, yes, it's a point of destiny, yes.
Yes, I'm going to tell Saya
Yes, in Sumas, this time we're going to do something a little different from what we've done in the past
I'm going to do something different this time with a different kind of space and colors that I don't usually do...
I know, right?
I'm going to ask you two to go change your clothes.
And you, Ai-chan and Taya-chan, come on in!
Oh!
Ooh!
They're still hiding their eyes from the judges.
I'm still hiding them. I'm nervous.
It's like they're totally different, but they're not.
Cute. Cute.
Okay, we'll go first.
We came across this.
This set is too cute.
400,000 won.
This one costs 300,000 won.
It's a set-up.
I can't reach it.
I can feel the wall.
200,000 won? 200,000 won.
It's good quality.
So I thought, "Here it is! I thought.
I put it together later.
Fluffy.
Cute, isn't it?
Colors that feel like fall
It's so cute.
So cute!
So cute.
It's cute.
It's been a while.
So cute.
What's your point, Azara?
Well...
The first thing we decided on...
This knit.
It's a knit with a hood.
We thought it was really cute.
It's rare to see a gray-black one like this, Saya.
It's really rare.
Black is rare.
Usually...
I usually draw browns and browns.
But her voice is different... like Sayaya's.
Yay!
Thank you.
She's cute.
And yes.And yes.
I paid 200,000 won.
This time, the total was 169,000 won.
That's cheap!
I also bought a bag.
You did?
Yes, I did.
This and a beret.
A beret, a bag, a top and bottom, 160,000 won.
You can't see it. You can't see it.
Too invisible.
And that's where the appeal pint comes in!
We left 200 yen, or rather, we left
exactly
We used the advanced technique of spending exactly
We did it.
And that's how the introduction ended.
Three female staff members were going to judge us.
I'm so nervous
Big, big, big!
Well, we'll let you guys decide whether to go this way or that way.
Please enjoy our reactions.
Okay.
Let's do it!
Wow.
voodoo
s
goo goo
Middle
Sadness
Ah亲asta
I'm sorry
Okay.
Here we go!
Three people could crack it!
If there were three of us, two of us cracked it!
Who was that?
I'm so surprised.
You're the one who decided!
I want to know!
I like the way you two look.
I like the staff cap.
I'm sure you're right.
It is.
Cute.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
On my way to the back.
If I had found something good to shop for.
I never knew.
ens.
Then
The one who loses yesterday wins.
But I lost 200,000 가.
That's nothing.
Well, I thought it was autumnOh no, I thought it was fall.
I love this one too!
I've been coming to every storytelling session back in Japan.
It's all Spanfor, right?
I've been talking about it at the Korean Coalition.
One year every year.
Congratulations!
You win.
Surprise.
Congratulations.
You're so cute.
You're too funny.
I've never been shopping at a mall in Korea.
I've never been.
It was so much fun!
I hope you'll try to imitate me.
Try to imitate them too!
That's all I can say.
It was a lot of fun!
Thank you very much.
And that's it.
That's all for today's Korean Coalition.
Is there going to be a next one?
If there is, please take a look.
Thank you for watching.
Bye bye.
You look cute.
You look cute.Cute.
Cute.
ED.